<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Loot 5.0</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="title_activity_fullscreen">FullscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_current_mission">Current Mission</string>
    <string name="title_locator">Locator</string>
    <string name="title_stats">Stats</string>
    <string name="title_leaderBoard">LeaderBoard</string>
    <string name="duel_mode">Duel Mode</string>
    <string name="current_task">Current Task</string>


    <string name="title_activity_welcome">Home Screen</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>

    <string name="slide_1_title">Hello Gangsta!</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">Message</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">Title2</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">Message</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">Title3</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">Message</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">Title4</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">Message</string>

    <string name="play_again_desc">To see the welcome slider again, goto Settings -> apps -> welcome slider -> clear data</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>


    You have to ace the maze before any other player reaches, climb the leaderboard.
    Remember, there is only one who will win and rest all will perish.
    Quitters won’t see what remains next in their life.
    Cheaters will not see the next day.
    It’s a Win or None.
    Ace it or perish!
    Deal? It's the only way out.

    <string name="intro">In the vast desert of Arrakis, where sandstorms rage and giant sandworms roam, there lived a solitary figure named Paul. He was a nomad, a wanderer, traversing the dunes with only his instincts as his guide. Paul's ancestors had once been rulers of Arrakis, but now their empire lay in ruins, lost to the sands of time.</string>
    <string name="intro3">Missions will be given to the players on reaching certain checkpoints inside the campus.\n\nA riddle is to be asked in reference to the place. \nThe players can always skip a riddle to move to next checkpoint but it would result in losing of points.</string>
    <string name="about">Embark on an epic adventure with Zealicon'24 as we present the 5th edition of LOOT, Get ready to dive into an adrenaline-fueled experience like never before. With your GPS as your guide, navigate through a virtual desert landscape, encountering unexpected challenges and solving mind-bending puzzles along the way. Prepare yourself for an adventure that will push your limits and leave you craving for more. Get set to be enthralled!</string>
    <string name="ncs_hallmark">© Nibble Computer Society</string>
    <string name="how_to">Turn on your phone GPS if it’s off. For every mission, first reach the location by decoding the provided information.\n\n
    Every time you reach a correct location , your phone will vibrate and you will be given a puzzle. solve itto earn coins and be taken to the next mission if you wish to. However, keep in mind that there will be penalty for every mission dropped.\n\n
    Your number of coins will decide your rank on the leaderboard. At the end od 2 days of the event going live , the top player on the leaderboard will be decleared winners. Happy looting!! </string>
    <string name="intro_page2">One fateful day, Paul stumbled upon an ancient artifact buried beneath the shifting sands. It was a map, etched onto a piece of weathered parchment, depicting hidden chambers and secret passages beneath the desert. Intrigued by the discovery, Paul realized that this map held the key to untold riches, hidden deep within the heart of Arrakis.
But Paul was not alone in his quest. The treacherous Baron Harkonnen, ruler of Arrakis, had caught wind of Paul's discovery and coveted the treasure for himself. Determined to claim it at any cost, the Baron dispatched his minions to hunt down Paul and seize the map.</string>
    <string name="intro_page3">As Paul journeyed deeper into the desert, he faced perilous challenges at every turn. Sandstorms threatened to engulf him, and deadly traps lay in wait within the ancient ruins. But Paul pressed on, driven by the promise of wealth beyond imagination.
Along the way, Paul encountered allies who aided him in his quest. A fierce warrior named Stilgar, leader of the desert tribes, pledged his loyalty to Paul's cause. Together, they faced off against the Baron's forces in a thrilling showdown amidst the dunes.</string>
    <string name="intro_page4">Mission Will be given to the player on the reaching certain checkpoints within the given map.

A riddle is to be asked in referenced the place.

    The player can always skip a riddle to move to next Checkpoint but it would result in\n<b> LOOSING THE POINTS</b>!!</string>
</resources>
